prompt where the artwork is constructed from nothing into the final
composition. So basically what I'm essentially telling the model to do
at LGBT is analyze this image that I've generated and just create the video
prompt for me. You could also use this generic one here that I've generated
which essentially is just describing to do similar thing in terms of anime
all the layers. It's just not being specific to the image. You can try both. I've
had good results with just a generic template and also had good results
with specific prompt templates. So as you can see here it's now crafting this
and it will be obviously referencing specific things in terms of how to animate
them which sometimes it adheres to it. Sometimes it doesn't. My god look at the
size of this prompt. Oh my god. So now we're just going to copy this. I'm going to
go into artless, go to video, see that. I'm going to use fast just because it's
cheaper. You can use fast mini and 2.0. I found the results are like every
generation looks different but I wouldn't say 2.0 looks necessarily any better
than fast. Like some generations I've had fast looks really good. Some mini looks
okay. Some 2.0 looks okay. And so I would always go with fast and also say it to
7.20. Five seconds is I found pretty good. You can go shorter. You can go longer.
I'm going to upload the image reference in here and then I'm going to copy and
paste in my prompt. Okay that's saying it's over the 5,000 world limit. No problem.
I'm just going to say reduce this to under 5,000 characters and not a problem.
That should just condense it down. I'll be honest. I've used this before and I've
never had one that long but that's not a problem. I don't think it's too far over.
So we just copy that, paste that in, generate. What I'll do is I'll generate a few
of these on each of the different models just so you can see the difference in
output. Let's go 7.80, generate and let's finally go cdance 2.0 which is
going to burn all my credits. Definitely don't 4k. Oh my god. Don't use 4k on
cdance. It's like $10.15 for like 10.15 seconds. 720. Very happy at 720. I have
actually just uploaded the wrong image for all of those as well. I have
uploaded the 9x16 and I'm asking for 16x9. Not a problem. Let's actually just
change this to 9x16 for all of them and just see what happens here because I
actually don't know how that's going to turn out. I've put the 9x16
image in and asked for 16x9 output which is fine. Let's just change that to 9x16
and then finally on the fast model. This one is a set to auto. Those are the
ones that weren't. Some reason didn't set to auto. So generating 6 here. We've
got 16x9 ones. Maybe this one actually isn't 9x16. Right. So these have
almost generated. Just waiting for this one here. That's fine. This one is the
cdance 2.0 fast. Not too bad. I love that includes the sound effects. If you don't
want the sound effects and you don't want the music you can just prompt at the
end like no music or no SFX. I personally like having the SFX music. You
could probably get rid of. You just prompt it to say get rid of the music. But
that's pretty good. The only part I don't like is that bit there. It's a bit
strange but overall as you can see fairly easy to do and get a quite a nice
flowing animation. Let's look at this next one. Okay this is the 16x9 one. This is
the cdance 2.0 mini model. Perhaps this is because it's 16x9 or perhaps it's the
mini model and it's just too difficult. See that's that shit. That's not very
good. We'll have a look at the other mini model one as well and see whether it
also does bad of which case I would rule out using the mini model for this one.
I said I have used the mini model before and it's done all right job but in my
opinion fast is the most optimum model for these in terms of credits and also
doing a decent.